本字幕由高清電臺整理發佈，更多高清電影請訪問
https://gaoqing.fm
本字幕由@老婆的小三@翻譯製作校正，如有錯誤，請自行修改。
我告訴過你，我不想要打針。
I don't need it. I'm telling you.
就因為你現在不覺得噁心了，並不意味著你不需要注射。
Just because you don't feel sick now doesn't mean you don't need the shot.
我從不生病，好嗎？你可以拿去給巴里。
I never get sick, okay? You can take that and give it to Barry.
-他總是流鼻涕.。-你在這裏說什麼屁話？
-His nose is always running. -What are you giving me shit for?
我今天早些時候見過你。我們打了個招呼。我說“科爾”你說“黛西先生”
I saw you earlier today. We said hi. I said, "Cole." You said, "Mr. Daisy."
你今天到底怎麼了？我的意思是，這只是一根針而已，夥計。
Why are you giving me shit today? I mean, it's just a needle, man.
該死，過來，打針。沒什麼可害怕的。
Damn. Come here, get the shot. Ain't nothing to be scared of.
有62個孩子已經打了，什麼問題都沒有。
There's 62 kids came here, got a shot, no problem.
你都進來十分鐘了吧？外面還有84個孩子要我給他們打針。趕緊好嗎？
You come in here, take ten minutes? I got 84 kids more to go. Okay?
我們是男孩。冷靜點。靠，夥計。要拍這張照片嗎？
We're boys. Be cool. Shit, man. Are you gonna take this shot?
到這邊來，照一照，就像你要拍屁股一樣。
Step over here and take the shot, just like you'd take some ass.
沒有什麼可害怕的。
There's nothing to be scared of.
我不害怕。
I'm not scared.
【風騷小保姆】
娘炮！
Pussy!
你知道五月花上只生了一個孩子嗎？
Did you know only one baby was born on the Mayflower?
那有多瘋狂？
How crazy is that shit?
他的名字，字面上叫歐瑪納斯。
His name was literally Oceanus.
他甚至沒有國籍。
He didn't even have a nationality.
我猜只是個海中公民。
Just a citizen of the sea, I guess.
你在哪門課上學的這些？
What class did you learn that in?
沒有人能夠在課堂上學到這些東西。這是我在互聯網上學到的知識。
[scoffs] No one learns anything in class. That's why we have the Internet.
那是我爸爸。
There's my dad.
媚蘭，過來。
[Melanie's dad] Melanie, get over here.
這是他高中時的夢想之車.。
It was his high-school dream car.
離婚後他得到了它，讓媽媽很嫉妒，但是..。
He got it after the divorce to make Mom jealous, but...
-因為是輛車，所以也沒有什麼。- 現在。
-it didn't work because it's a car. -Now.
爸爸，我們能送科爾回家嗎？
Dad, can we give Cole a ride home?
科爾，你父母在等你坐公共汽車回家嗎？
Cole, are your parents expecting you to take the bus home?
-我猜是的.。-是的，他們是。
-I guess so. -Yeah, they are.
那麼，你應該坐公共汽車，好嗎，夥計？
So, you should take the bus, okay, sport?
抱歉，夥計。不過，我們再見，鄰居，嗯？
Sorry, dude. I'll see you, though, neighbor, huh?
-我沒有----那是什麼？
-I didn't-- -What's that?
-國家賽車協會，賤人。哇！- 爸爸-。
-NASCAR Nation, bitch. Whoo! -[Melanie] Dad--
爸爸！
[Melanie] Dad!
噢--哇，噢--哇。哇，哇-哇.。
[Jeremy] Ooh-whah, ooh-whah. Ooh-whah, ooh-whah.
喔 喔 喔
Well, well, well.
嘿，結腸鏡檢查。檢查得怎麼樣？
[Jeremy] Hey, Colonoscopy. How's it hanging?
我不知道。好嗎？
I don't know. Okay?
說到結腸鏡檢查，檢查的時候你的蛋蛋掉下來了嗎？
Well, speaking of hanging, have your balls dropped yet?
我沒聽明白。
I didn't catch that.
我說：“你為什麼對我的蛋蛋那麼感興趣？”
I said, "Why are you so interested in my balls?"
他最不關心的就是你的蛋蛋。
Last thing he cares about is your balls.
是的，因為星期六，我和雪麗·麥肯太爾上了床。
[Jeremy] Yeah, 'cause on Saturday, I hooked up with Shelly MacEntyre.
大二的時候？
The sophomore?
大二，但在很多方面，她都是大四學生。
The sophomore. But in many ways, she was a senior.
-我不相信你。-你不需要相信他。
-I don't believe you. -You don't need to believe him.
這並不是你說不相信，就不是真的。
It's not like your belief will validate what happens to his dick.
想知道是怎麼回事嗎？
Wanna know how it was?
不，不是真的。
No, not really.
嗯，你看，作為一個14歲的孩子，在那種情況下。
Well, see, as a 14-year-old in that kind of situation
一個16歲的孩子看起來像雪麗·麥肯太爾。
with a 16-year-old that looks like Shelly MacEntyre,
實在是讓人無法拒絕那種誘惑。
it was overwhelming, man.
她是個女人。
I mean, she is a woman.
完全成熟了，夥計。太瘋狂了，夥計。這是... 。
Fully-developed, man. It's crazy, man. It's... [grunts]
老兄，你知道我在說什麼嗎？
Man, you know what I'm saying?
我說，你知道我在說什麼嗎？
I said, do you know what I'm saying?
你剛才說，我信不信你沒關係。
You just said it didn't matter if I believed you.
-嗯，我改變主意了，賤人.。-對不起，我不是-。
-Well, I changed my mind, bitch. -Sorry, I wasn't--
噢，天啊，他好弱。
[Jeremy] Oh, my God. He's so weird. [laughs]
哇，哇-哇.。哇，哇-哇.。
Ooh-whah, ooh-whah. Ooh-whah, ooh-whah.
嘿！
[woman] Hey!
剛才是你把科爾推倒在地上的嗎？
Did you just touch Cole?
-那如果是我呢？- 傑瑞米，過來看看。
-So, what if I did? -[woman] Jeremy, check it out.
再想想科爾..。
You so much as think about Cole again...
而我要...
and I'm gonna...
瘋婊子。
You crazy bitch.
♪女孩子們想成為她 ♪。
♪ The girls wanna be her ♪
-現在趕緊滾！
-Now get out of here!
在我要揍你之前，你這個小王八蛋
Before I run you over, you little Pap smear.
-嘿，科利. - 嘿，比。
-Hey, Coley. -[Cole] Hey, Bee.
這是新的眼鏡。
These are new.
是的，我有時得戴上它。
Yeah, I have to wear them sometimes.
據說它們能增強我的左眼。
They supposedly help strengthen my left eye,
-但我看不出有什麼區別.。-對我來說，你看上去很強壯.。
-but I can't tell the difference. -You look pretty strong to me.
手掌擦破皮了？
You skin your palms?
-不痛.。-是的，是的.。到這兒來。
-It doesn't hurt. -Yeah, it does. Come here.
-他們經常欺負你是不是？-不是。
-They bother you a lot? -No.
撒謊的時候你會轉移視線，老兄。是那些經常扔雞蛋到你家裏的人嗎？
You look away when you lie, dude. They the ones that egg your house?
你得打他們的雞巴。
You gotta punch them in the dick.
如果他們在追你，等他們快抓到你了。
And if they're chasing you, wait until they've almost got you,
像一袋石頭一樣摔倒下來，然後當他們絆到你時，
drop like a bag of rocks, then when they trip over you,
他們就在撲倒在地上，然後你去踢他們的雞巴。
and they're on the ground, kick them in the dick.
-嘿，那麼，告訴我，大家都好嗎？-很好，我想。
-Hey, so, tell me, how's the folks? -Better, I think.
在酒店工作怎麼樣？
Hotel therapy's working?
不，別這樣，太棒了。
No, come on, it's great.
我的意思是，他們很高興，我們可以出去玩，而我得到報酬。
I mean, they're happy, we get to hang out, and I get paid.
-我就像你的小新教徒。- 什麼？
-I'm like your little Protestant. -[chuckles] What?
因為，我得付錢讓你跟我出去玩。
'Cause, like, I have to pay you to hang out with me.
是不是想說“妓女”？
Are you trying to say "prostitute"?
天哪-。
Oh, my God--
不，那會讓我成為妓女，讓你的父母成為客戶。
No, that would make me the prostitute and your parents the clients.
這是一個可怕的比喻。這是有史以來最糟糕的一次。
That is a terrible analogy. That is the worst one ever.
-哦...-此外。
-Oh... -Besides,
不管怎麼說，我都想和你在一起。
I'd wanna hang out with you either way.
真的?。
Really?
百分之百。
One hundred percent.
在你太酷不能和我一起玩之前，我最多有兩年的時間。
I got two years tops before you're too cool to hang out with me.
我永遠不會太酷。
I'll never be too cool.
嘿，那是你樹屋的屋頂嗎？
Hey, is that the roof of your tree house?
是的，我們剛開始把它取下來。
[Cole] Yeah, we just started to take it down.
--我--我不在乎。我是說，我的，呃-。
I-- I don't care. I mean, my, uh--
反正樹屋是給孩子的。
Tree houses are for kids anyway.
裏面有很多美好的回憶，對吧？
There's a lot of good memories in there, right?
嗯。
Yeah.
明晚。你，我，派對。
All right, tomorrow night. You. Me. Party.
聽起來不錯。
Sounds good.
手指。
E.T. fingers.
-好的.。再見，-再見，蜜蜂。
-All right. See you, Cee. -Bye-bye, Bee.
得把門修好。你還把這個給我，對嗎？
Gotta get that door fixed. You're still giving this to me, right?
-百分之百。-不能在我的車上有粘粘的門.。
-One hundred percent. -Can't have a sticky door on my car.
媽媽！
Hey, Mom!
嘿！科爾。
[Mom] Hey! Cole.
科爾，你能給我一個老鼠夾嗎？
Cole, can you hand me one of those traps, please?
給你。
Ow.
-謝謝.。你好，-你好。
-Thanks. Hi. -Hi.
謝謝你，兄弟。
[grunts] Thanks, buddy.
上帝，上帝。
God. God.
媽媽，你怎麼會在下面？下麵看起來會有一萬億隻蜘蛛。
Mom, how can you be under there? There's like a trillion spiders.
科爾，我不喜歡這裏。這下麵最糟糕了。
[Mom] Cole, I don't like it under here. It's pretty much the worst.
-媽媽，你認為我是個娘炮嗎？- 啊。
-Do you think I'm a pussy, Mom? -[thud] Ow.
你知道那個詞的意思嗎？
[Mom] Do you know what that word means?
是的，就像，不像男人，什麼都怕。-噢.。
-[Cole] Yeah, like, afraid of everything. -Ow.
嗯..。
Um...
哈。
Huh.
呃..
Well... [sighs]
我覺得...你在你的生命中。
I think... you are at a time in your life
很多事情都很可怕。
where a lot of things are scary.
但隨著年齡的增長，同樣的事情也會停止讓你害怕。
But as you get older, those same things will stop frightening you as much.
好吧。
Okay?
一切都會好起來的。
It's gonna be okay.
你真應該弄點噴霧劑來殺死裏面的蜘蛛。
[Cole] You should really get some bug spray to kill the spiders in there.
他們對你們做了什麼？他們吃其他的髒蟲子。
What have they done to you? They eat other dirty bugs.
嘿，你能給我來杯檸檬水嗎？
Hey, will you get me a lemonade?
-是的.。-謝謝.。
-Yep. -Thanks.
媽媽，我知道“娘炮”也是“陰道”的意思。我不是弱智。
Mom, I know "pussy" also means "vagina." I'm not retarded.
科爾·詹森。別說“弱智”
Cole Johnson. Do not say "retarded."
-但是我可以說“娘炮”或“陰道”--“
-But I can say "pussy" or "vagi--"
別說了，好嗎？
Don't say it, okay?
去拿檸檬水給我。
Go get me a lemonade.
天啊，他說“娘炮”
Oh, my God, he said "pussy."
吸氣。呼出。
[man] Breathe in. Breathe out.
放鬆。- 好的。
-Unclench that sphincter. -[Cole] Okay.
-帶著眼鏡看的清晰嗎？-看起來不錯.。
-How those mirrors looking? -Looking good.
刹車？
Parking brakes?
沒有。
Nope.
-雙手？-十和二。
-Hands? -Ten and two.
開始。
Engage.
爸爸，你知道嗎，每天有七個青少年死於開車？
Dad, did you know that seven teenagers die a day from driving?
真的?哇。
Really? Wow.
你知道嗎，呃，每天有14名青少年死於過度擔憂？
Did you know that, uh, 14 teenagers die a day from over-worrying?
我上網了。
I went on the Internet,
還有他們的照片。他們是這樣死的。
and there's pictures of them. They die like this:
或許下個星期。
Maybe next week.
好吧，兄弟，當然。想交換嗎？
All right, buddy, sure. You wanna swap?
-是的.。-很好。明白了。做得很好。
-Yeah. -Good. All right. You did good.
你發動汽車，系上安全帶。
You started the car, you put the seat belt on.
別擔心，夥計。不急。
Don't worry about it, pal. There's no rush.
害怕是可以的。沒什麼大不了的，好嗎？
It's okay to be scared. It's not a big deal, okay?
嘿，我問你個問題。做你的朋友-。
Hey, let me ask you something. Do your friends--
他們會因為你有保姆而取笑你嗎？
Do they make fun of you for having a babysitter?
對。
Yeah.
但後來他們看到了她，就開始嫉妒了。
But then they see her and get really jealous.
是的，該死，是的，他們知道。
Yeah. Heck, yeah, they do. [chuckles]
我不知道你的情況，夥計，但我覺得自己像個員警。
I don't know about you, buddy, but I'm feeling like a cop.
我想要一些甜甜圈。
I'm craving some donuts.
好的！
[Dad] All right!
看什麼呢？
What are you watching?
你爸爸在為瘋狂廣告人節目而大發雷霆。
Your dad is bingeing on Mad Men.
又來了。
Again.
你不會喜歡的。
You wouldn't like it.
HBO上有嗎？
It's on HBO?
不，不是--不是很黃很暴力的東西，夥計。
-[chuckles] -No, it's not-- It's not dirty, buddy.
不在HBO頻道上。
It's not on HBO.
有很多季很多集，你知道的。所以，它可能會看的你頭疼。
It's dense, you know. So, it might go over your head.
等你長大一點，我們可以一起看。
When you get a little older, we'll binge-watch it together.
在那怎麼樣？
How about that?
好的。-科爾，你能清理一下玩具嗎？
-[Cole] All right. -Cole, will you clean up the toys
在走廊上那些？
in the hallway for me?
好吧，媽媽，天啊。
Okay, Mom. Jeez.
謝謝。
Thank you.
乾淨多了。
[Cole] Much cleaner.
管他呢？
Who cares?
嘿，哦。
Hey. Oh.
嘿，那看起來一點也不安全。
Hey, that doesn't seem safe at all.
-我能應付.。-是的.。不，我明白。
-I can handle it. -Yeah. No, I get it.
停下，停下。
Stop. Stop.
把刀遞給我。
And hand me the knife.
太棒了。你為什麼用刀把車割開？
Fabulous. Why you cutting up your car with a knife?
我要把車頂換個靠背，
I'm gonna switch the roof with a fastback,
-所以是空氣動力學的。嗯-嗯。
-so it's aerodynamic. -Uh-huh.
它會使我在轉彎時更有力。
It's gonna give me more downforce on the turns.
當它撞到坡道時，它就會翻滾。
When it hits the ramp, it'll do a barrel roll
並按我的計畫撞進墜機區-。
and smash into the crash zone exactly how I intend--
明白明白。我讚揚你對空氣動力學的熱情。
Got it, got it. I applaud your passion for aerodynamics.
我當然喜歡，但只有在你切牛排的時候才用的到這個。
I absolutely do, but only use this if you're cutting a flank steak.
別那麼做。那是我的工作。
And don't do that. That's my job.
如果你這都已經會弄了，在這個家我還能夠做什麼？
And if you take that job, what am I doing at this house?
要我把它放回去嗎？
Do you want me to put it back?
不，我要把這個放在洗碗機裏。
[Dad] No. I'm gonna put this in the dishwasher,
因為它已經粘上了我的汗水弄髒了。
'cause it's coated in my sweat and fear.
父母又要去旅行了。我覺得他們目的是為了做愛。
My parents are going away again. I think they go to have sex,
但這讓我覺得他們想要離開我。
but it just makes me feel like they go to get away from me.
他們肯定在做愛。
They're definitely having sex.
他們可能也會在你回家的時候發生性關係。
They probably have sex when you're home, too.
另外，我打賭蜜蜂也會帶男孩子在你的地方一直在做愛。
Besides, I bet Bee has boys over at your place all the time doing it.
不，不。
Nope. No.
不行!不可能。
No way. Not a chance.
是的，保姆就是這麼做的。
Yeah. That's what babysitters do.
他們把孩子們放下來，把他們的男朋友偷偷帶進來。然後做愛。
They put the kids down, sneak their boyfriends in. Doing it.
說真的，她睡著後你有沒有醒過？
Seriously, have you ever been awake after she's fallen asleep?
我敢說，如果今天晚上你不睡覺，你就知道是怎麼回事了。
I dare you to stay up tonight. You'll see.
我會發現的。
I'm gonna find out.
-Perv。-不！我要窒息了！
-Perv. -No! I'm choking!
娘炮！
Pussy!
親愛的，我不是在催你，但我們不是應該在五點離開嗎？
Honey, not that I'm rushing you, but weren't we supposed to leave at five?
不，親愛的，為了避免假日交通。
[Mom] No, honey, 5:30 to avoid holiday traffic.
我們本該在五點離開的。
We were supposed to leave at five.
不要移動傢俱。我們剛把地板擦乾淨。
Don't move the furniture around. We just did the floors.
-我不想讓你媽媽大喊大叫。- 明白了。
-I don't want your mom yelling. -[Cole] Got it.
我不對你大喊大叫。我只會用大寫字母說話。
I don't yell at you. I just speak in all caps.
對，這就是我喜歡她的地方。
Right. That's what I love about her.
-這裏。拿著這個。可能是蜜蜂。
-[doorbell rings] -Here. Get that. It's probably Bee.
好的。
Okay.
你能快點嗎？- 是的。
Can you hurry up? - Yes.
-怎麼了，希？-什麼事，比？
-What up, Cee? -What up, Bee?
嘿，蜜蜂，你好嗎？-哦，你知道，不能抱怨。
-[Mom] Hey, Bee. How are you? -Oh, you know, can't complain.
很好，-這個週末去哪兒。
-[Mom] Good. -Where to this weekend?
-呃... 凱悅酒店。大酒店。-嗯！
-Uh... The Hyatt. Living large. -Mm!
找不到！
[Dad] Can't find it!
呃，試試你的內衣褲下面的抽屜。
Uh, try the bottom drawer under your Invisalign.
反正你知道怎麼做的了。
Um, anyway, you know the drill.
沒有暴力電影，沒有垃圾食品，十點前睡覺。
No violent movies, no junk food, bed by ten.
媽媽，-10點30分前上床嗎。
-[Cole] Mom. -Bed by 10:30?
你是認真的嗎？- 還有別的嗎？
-[Cole] You serious? -[Bee] Anything else?
臥室裏沒有泳衣。
Uh, there is not a bathing suit in that bedroom.
那麼，親愛的，我不知道該告訴你什麼。
[Mom] Then, honey, I don't know what to tell you.
-我不在上面。- 好的。
-I'm not up there. -[Dad] Okay.
-他肯定會帶著他的牛仔褲短褲。- 媽媽，他叫他們小丑。
-He's totally gonna bring his jean shorts. -[Cole] Mom, he calls them jorts.
-嗯，我們會沒事的.。我能應付他的。-我知道。你是最棒的。
-Well, we'll be fine. I can handle him. -I know. You're the best.
- 我帶著我的軍裝。-我就知道！
-[Dad] I'm bringing my jorts. -[Mom] I knew it!
- 我帶著我的軍裝。-我就知道.。太棒了。
-[Dad] I'm bringing my jorts. -I knew it. Great.
我會成為世界各地女人羡慕的對象。
I will be the envy of women everywhere.
嘿，嗯，蜜蜂，如果有麻煩，給我們打電話，好嗎？
Hey, uh, Bee, call us if there's any trouble, okay?
-科爾，別惹麻煩了。- 爸爸，我知道。
-Cole, don't cause any trouble. -[Cole] Dad, I know.
知道嗎，親愛的？
You know what, honey?
-你注射了流感疫苗，所以不要用力。-媽媽。
-You got your flu shot, so no exertion. -[Cole] Mom.
-是的，不能到處跑.。棋盤遊戲。- 明白了。好吧。
-Yeah, no running around. Board games. -[Cole] Got it. Okay?
嘿，科爾，記住，你現在是家裏的人了。
Hey, Cole, remember, you're the man of the house now.
太貼心了。就是你。
That's sweet. You are.
-我們愛你.。再見，比，-我愛你。玩得開心!。
-We love you. Bye, Bee. -I love you. Have fun.
- 但別太開心。-不要太多。
-[Dad] But not too much fun. -[Mom] Not too much.
【佛加特的“我只想和你做愛”在演奏】。
[Foghat's "I Just Want to Make Love to You" playing]
♪我不要你做我的麵包♪
♪ I don't want you cook my bread ♪
♪我不想讓你給我鋪床♪
♪ I don't want you make my bed ♪
♪我不希望你是真的♪
♪ I don't want you to be true ♪
♪我只是想跟你做愛♪
♪ I just want to make love to you ♪
♪我不想讓你成為奴隸♪
♪ I don't want you be no slave ♪
♪我不想讓你傷心和憂鬱♪
♪ I don't want you to be sad and blue ♪
♪我只是想跟你做愛♪
♪ I just want to make love to you ♪
你潛水不可能有我厲害的。
[Cole] No way you're gonna beat my dive.
所以，你基本上是說，星際夢之隊在執行任務。
So, you're basically saying, intergalactic dream team on a mission.
-是的.。所以，有一個史詩反派，對嗎？-沒錯.。
-Yeah. So, there's an epic villain, right? -Right.
好吧，那麼，你必須填滿一艘星際飛船..。
Okay, so, you have to fill a starship...
充滿了最好的人、外星人或機器人來把他們打倒。
full of the best people or aliens or robots to take them down.
-我有幾個座位？-五個。
-How many seats have I got? -Five.
-五個？-六，如果你需要一個二重唱的話。
-Five? -Six, if you need, like, a duo.
但是你不能有捕食者和異形。
But you can't have a Predator and Xenomorph.
他們會打架的。任務是徒勞的。
They'd fight. The mission would be futile.
不，不，好吧，我明白了。
No, no, okay, I get it.
明白了。一..柯克。
All right. One... Kirk.
二，皮卡德。
Two, Picard.
第三，來自獨立日的威爾·史密斯和傑夫·戈德布拉。
Three, Will Smith and Jeff Goldblum from Independence Day.
五，裏普利，六..。準備好了嗎？
Five, Ripley, and six... Are you ready for this shit?
一個異形卵。
A Xenomorph egg.
-不行.。-是的.。
-No way. -Yeah.
是的，是的，好的，這是計畫。
Yes. Yes. Okay. Here's the plan.
柯克和皮卡德隊向隊長靠近，然後當他們接近時，
Kirk and Picard team up to captain, then when they get close,
他們派威爾和戈德布盧姆到巢穴裏去。
they send Will and Goldblum to get inside the lair.
-他們有這方面的經驗。-公平。
-They have experience with that. -Fair.
裏普利一直在抱怨
Now, this whole time, Ripley's been bitching
關於異形蛋和狗屎，因為這是她的舉動。
about the Xenomorph egg and shit, 'cause that's her move.
但她必須這麼做。
But she's gotta do this.
-這是拯救世界的唯一方法.。-宇宙。
-It's the only way to save the world. -The universe.
對。一點兒沒錯。
Right! Exactly!
威爾和戈德布盧姆把她弄進巢穴。
So, Will and Goldblum get her inside the lair.
裏普利親自下蛋，臉擁抱者攻擊大壞蛋！
Ripley personally drops off the egg, the facehugger attacks the big bad!
裏普利回到威爾和戈德布盧姆，大壞蛋襲擊他們，
Ripley makes it back to Will and Goldblum, the big bad attacks them,
他們險些逃脫。
they narrowly escape.
柯克和皮卡德補給罩，當航天器返回家園，
Kirk and Picard supply cover as the spacecraft returns home,
然後他們從那裏平靜下來。與此同時，大壞蛋開始感覺像屎一樣..。
then they peace out of there. Meanwhile, the big bad starts feeling like shit...
他出局了！
He's out!
誰說他是他？
Who said he was a he?
-閉嘴.。一個女人剛剛拯救了銀河系。-面孔擁抱者是女性嗎？
-Shut up. A woman just saved the galaxy. -Are facehuggers female?
不因為他們有雞巴。
No, 'cause they got dicks.
哦，你是說，拯救銀河系需要一根雞巴。
Oh, so, you're saying it took a dick to save the galaxy.
-我想要一份工作.。-
-I want a do-over. -
-我想要一份工作.。-不行-翻過來。
-I want a do-over. -No do-overs.
來吧(趕快)。外星人不遵守我們原始的性別刻板印象。
Come on. Aliens don't abide by our primitive gender stereotypes.
-做的都做完了.。-你真爛.。
-What's done is done. -You suck.
-你真爛，我希望你死掉。-沒有我你活不下去
-You suck, and I hope you die. -You couldn't live without me.
這肯定會影響我的收入。那麼，你可能是對的。
It would definitely affect my income. So, you're probably right.
-比薩！-比薩！
-Pizza! -Pizza!
大印度酋長。如此特別。所以淩駕於法律之上。
[Bee and actor 1] Big Indian Chief. So special. So above the law.
我告訴過你，你會犯錯誤的，我會等你。
I told you, you'd make a mistake, and I'd be waiting.
看起來我別無選擇，是嗎？
[Cole and actor 2] It doesn't look like I have any choice, does it?
對。不知道。
[Bee and actor 1 laugh] That's right. You don't.
我要把這個右腳...。
[Cole and actor 2] I'm gonna take this right foot...
而我要在你的臉的那一邊打你。
and I'm gonna whop you on that side of your face.
想知道什麼嗎？
And you wanna know something?
對此你什麼也做不了。
There's not a damn thing you're gonna be able to do about it.
真的嗎？- [科爾和演員2]真的。
-[Bee and actor 1] Really? -[Cole and actor 2] Really.
殺死那個印度狗娘養的。
Kill that Indian son of a bitch.
覺得我父母會離婚嗎？
Think my parents are gonna get a divorce?
我不知道，夥計。我真希望不是這樣。
I don't know, man. I hope not.
梅勒妮的父母離婚了。她媽媽和她男朋友住在一起。
Melanie's parents got divorced. Her mom lives with her boyfriend.
那真噁心。
That's gross.
那不是街對面那個可愛的女孩嗎？
Isn't that the cute chick across the street?
德雷爾女士不可愛。她真噁心。
Ms. Dryer is not cute. She's gross.
她男朋友差不多20歲了。
Her boyfriend's like 20.
不是她。媚蘭。
Not her. Melanie.
我不會說她很可愛。
I wouldn't say she's cute.
哦，我會的。我覺得她超可愛。
Oh, I would. I would say she's super-duper cute.
我知道你想做什麼。不會成功的。
[stammers] I see what you're trying to do. It's not gonna work.
隨便啦。你想讓你的舌頭去舔她。
Whatever. You want your tongues to touch.
不，不可能。
Nope. No way.
-哦，你在否認。-你是個...混蛋。
-Oh, you're in denial. -You're an... asshole.
天啊，太棒了。
Oh, my God. That was so great.
但如果你父母分手，你會沒事的。
But you'll be all right if your parents break up.
我是說...你得照顧好自己。
I mean... you just gotta take care of yourself.
先找出你想要的，然後盡你所能去得到它。
Gotta figure out what you want, and then do what you can to get it.
啊，該死的，夥計，已經很晚了。
Ah, shit, dude, it's super late.
-我不累。-嗯，我知道你不累。是的。
-I'm not tired. -Well, I know you're not. I am.
如果我給你一次機會，你會上床睡覺嗎？
[snaps fingers] If I give you a shot, will you go to bed?
-我不知道。-也許，我有兩個方法。
-I don't know, maybe. -I'll make it a double.
-你會睡得像塊石頭。-好的.。
-You'll sleep like a rock. -Okay.
給你，我的好先生。
Here you are, my good sir.
不要對你的父母說這件事。
Don't say a word of this to your parents.
爸爸一直讓我喝麥克的酒。
My dad lets me drink Mike's all the time.
老兄，這是我一生中聽過的最酷的事情。
Dude, that is the coolest thing I've ever heard in my life.
難道你不來一杯？
You're not gonna do it with me?
行，當然。馬上回來。
All right, sure. I'll be right back.
難道你已經喝了？趁我不在的時候。
You did it without me?
乾杯！
Cheers.
哇。
Whew.
她要上床了。
She's getting laid. -[chuckles]
-我會發現的。-哇，想想都刺激。
-I'm gonna find out. -Wow, I'm impressed.
但是，偷看別人做愛，好像不太好。
That's actually pervy, though, watching people do it.
我不是變態。我只是想知道我睡覺後會發生什麼。
I'm not a perv. I just wanna know what happens after I go to sleep.
我得掛了。
I gotta go.
不
-No.
請進。
Enter.
困嗎？
You sleepy?
是的，我真的很累。
Yeah, I'm really tired.
好好休息。派對明天繼續。
Well, rest up. The party continues tomorrow.
需要什麼嗎？明白了。
You need anything? All right.
-蜜蜂？-什麼？
-Bee? -Yeah?
我很高興認識你，而且你對我這麼好！
Thanks for knowing me and treating me like I was okay.
怎麼了？你沒事吧？
You don't think you're okay?
我是說..。
I mean...
我想有正常的感覺，但..。
I wanna feel normal, but...
大部分時間我都覺得很奇怪。
I just feel weird most of the time.
嗯，我喜歡奇怪。
Well, I like weird.
一直以來。
All of the time.
想像一下，當你大四的時候，所有的女孩都會愛你。
So, just imagine how all the girls are gonna love you when you're a senior.
明早見。
See you in the morning.
晚安，夥計。
Good night, dude.
在狂歡了嗎？
Ew. Orgy?
狂歡？
Orgy?
旋轉它。
Spin it.
哇！
[Allison] Whoo!
是啊！- 我們點燃了。點燃了。
-[Max] Yeah! -[John] We lit. We lit.
相信我。
Truth me.
這裏的每個人，你最想和誰上床？
Out of everybody here, who would you want to sleep with the most?
-索尼婭.。- 哦，是的。
-Sonya. -[Allison] Ooh, yeah.
百分之百。
Hundred percent.
-來吧.。-山姆，到你了，大個子。
-Come on. -Sam, you're a close second, stud.
該死，-好吧。輪到我了。
-[John] Damn. -Okay. My turn.
各位。- 對這個壞女孩。
-[Allison] Yo, people. -[John] To this bad girl.
蜜蜂，真心話還是大冒險。
Bee, truth or dare.
大冒險。
Dare.
-我要你吻了這裏的每個人。
-I dare you to kiss everyone here. -[Allison chuckles]
-是的。- 哦，是的。
-Yes. -[Allison] Ooh, yeah.
她有那個膽量。- 我需要看。
-[John] She got balls. -[Sonya] I need to watch.
好吧。
All right.
-這就是我在說的。- 我為此感到興奮。
-That's what I'm talking about. -[Sonya] I'm excited for that.
那就是我要找的全部。- 等一下。
-[Max] That's all I'm looking for. -[Allison] Hold on.
我們來吧。
[John] Let's go.
我準備好了。
I'm ready.
♪人人都喜歡陽光♪
♪ Everybody loves the sunshine ♪
我知道是你，弗雷多。我知道那是你。
[in deep voice] I know it was you, Fredo. I know it was you.
-謝謝.。-那是指環王嗎？
-Thank you. -Is that Lord of the Rings?
那是教父的第二部分。
That was The Godfather Part II .
我愛她。
I love her.
- 好的，這很容易。來吧(趕快)。- [馬克斯]那很好。
-[Bee] All right, this is easy. Come on. -[Max] That was pretty good.
[鞠躬哇“我要糖果”的演奏]。
[Bow Wow Wow's "I Want Candy" playing]
哦，好吧。
[Max] Oh, okay.
你們都排練過了。
[John] Y'all rehearsed this.
♪太陽下山時去看他♪
♪ Go to see him when the sun goes down ♪
♪城裏沒有比這更好的男孩了♪
♪ Ain't no finer boy in town ♪
♪醫生給你點的東西你是我的人嗎♪
♪ You're my guy What the doctor ordered ♪
♪這麼甜你讓我流口水♪
♪ So sweet you make my mouth water ♪
♪要糖果嗎♪
♪ I want candy ♪
♪嗯。♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪要糖果嗎♪
♪ I want candy ♪
等等，快來親我-。
[pants] Wait, just give me--
給我一分鐘，讓我塗一個唇膏先。
Give me a second to process that shit.
- 你是由瑞克·詹姆斯撫養長大的？-我想要從來一次。
-[John] You raised by Rick James? -I'm thinking a redo.
-太棒了。
-That's amazing. -[laughing]
一定要跟你吻好久，因為我是黑人。看到了嗎？
Make sure it's real nice and long for you, because I'm black. See that?
就這樣。嗯。
There you go. Mm.
-該死，是的。
-[Bee giggles] -Fuck, yeah.
來吧(趕快)。
Come on.
-哇！- 是啊！
-Whoo! -[Sonya] Yeah!
哦，蜜蜂！
[John] Oh, Bee!
蜜蜂，怎麼回事？
Bee, what the hell?
我給你塗了這麼浪漫的唇膏，你要舔我的臉嗎？
You give her that romantic shit, and you're gonna lick my face?
該死，這就是我的全部要求。
Damn, that's all I'm asking.
- 好的。- 他媽的。
-[Bee] All right. -[John] Freaky shit.
聞起來不錯。唾沫很好。今早刷牙了。
Smell good. The spit is nice. Brushed your teeth this morning.
好的。
[Max laughing] Okay.
真奇怪。- 你好。
-[John] Weird. -[Bee] Hi.
是啊！
-[John howling] -[Allison laughing] Yeah!
到薩米了。
[Max cat-calling] Sammy's turn.
薩米。
-[John laughing] -[Max chanting] Sammy.
- 她太性感了。- 好的。
-[Allison] She's so hot. -[John] Okay.
[好了，山姆，你來吧。
[Max] Come on, Sam. You got this.
和她親熱。
Make out with her.
對不起。
[Sam] I'm sorry.
這有點奇怪。我甚至都不認識你們。
This is kind of weird. I don't even really know you guys.
來吧，山姆，嚇到你了，好嗎？
[Max] Come on, Sam. Freak you out, there, stud?
-山姆，別傻了。- 我甚至不認識你們。
-Sam, don't be a puss. -[Sam] I don't even know you guys.
我不是。-我-我只是-。
[Sam] I'm not. I'm-- I just--
-你在盯著我看。- 噢，我們沒有在看。
-You're staring at me. -[Max] Oh, we're not looking.
嘿，這不奇怪。
[Allison] Hey, it's not weird.
- 嘿 是啊。
-[Bee] Hey. -[John] Yeah.
閉上眼睛。
Just close your eyes.
好吧。
Okay?
假裝他們根本不在這裏。
Pretend they're not even here.
你能做到的。
You can do this.
你來處理。
You got this.
僅僅因為我閉上眼睛並不意味著他們不在這裏。
Just because I close my eyes doesn't mean that they're not here.
你相信我媽？
Do you trust me?
對。
Yes.
放鬆點。
Just relax.
這不奇怪，好嗎？我們只是玩得開心。
It's not weird, okay? We're just having fun.
他走了。
There he goes.
噓。
Shh.
要知道。你在幫助我們實現一個偉大的目標。
You're helping fulfill a great purpose. Know this.
我不要做偉大的海豚
I don't wanna fulfill a great porpoise.
他剛才說的是“海豚”嗎？
[grunts] Did he just say "porpoise"?
喲，我想是他說的。
Yo, I think he did.
他甚至都不知道怎麼一回事
He didn't even get a chance to understand.
準備好了。
Ready?
準備好了。-是的.。
-[Sonya] Ready. -Yep.
哦，好吧。
-[John grunts] Oh, okay. -[exhales]
臥槽，這東西漏了。
[John] That shit leaking.
等等，等等。我覺得不起作用了。我覺得它沒血了。
Wait, hold on. My shit ain't working. I think it ran out of blood.
-哦，該死！-哦，該死的。
-Oh, shit! -Oh, shit.
噢，該死！
[John yells] Oh, shit!
所有的血都在他骨瘦如柴的人身上。
[Max] All that blood was just in his boner.
麥克斯，別笑，好嗎？約翰，放鬆。這血在為你服務。
Max, don't laugh, okay? John, relax. This blood is serving you.
我並沒有報名參加這個活動，幹嘛來為我服務。
I did not sign up for this shit to serve me in my mouth.
臥槽，這血還是熱的。我覺得他發燒了。
This shit's still warm. I think he got a fever.
你知道你報名到底為什麼的，想去唱片店嗎？約翰？
You know what you signed up for. You want to go platinum, John?
當你和魔鬼做交易時，事情會變得混亂。
Things can get messy when you make a deal with the devil.
現在把血收集起來。
Now collect it.
- 像這樣？- 給你。
-[John] Like this? -[Bee] There you go.
這要花多長時間？我只想讓我的願望快點變成現實。
[Allison] How long is this gonna take? I just want my shit to come true.
愛麗森，你們都會得到你們想要的。
[Bee] Allison, you'll all get what you want.
好的，我們開始吧。
Okay, let's go.
我認為這不好笑。看看我的衣服。
[John] I don't think this is funny. Look at my outfit.
我剛買到的這衣服，你知道嗎？七折買回來的。
I just got this shit, you feel me? Thirty percent off.
梅西的衣服。我不玩遊戲。
Macy's. Top rack. I don't play games.
你長得像嘉莉。
You look like Carrie,
-但是黑色的.。-嘉莉會更好的。
-but black. -Carrie would've been better black.
她會被軒尼詩所涵蓋的，好嗎？
She would have been covered in Hennessy, all right?
你穿的又是什麼玩意？看起來像大鳥的婊子。
What are you wearing? Looking like Big Bird's side bitch.
我剛從一場比賽中回來，來不及換，當然穿這身運動服了。
I just came from a game. That's why I'm wearing this, obviously.
我不會錯過的。
I was not gonna miss this.
看看這些鬼東西，怪不得病毒很難傳播。
Look at this shit. That would go viral so hard.
我是說，沒有人用人來祭祀的。
I mean, nobody's done human sacrifice.
人們總是做出人類的犧牲。
People have always done human sacrifice.
是的，但是，就像...不是在美國和熱帶的人在一起。
Yeah, but, like... not in America with hot people.
索尼婭，把箱子拿來。
Sonya, get the cases.
聽著，當你完蛋了。
Listen, when you're done being totally useless,
趕緊拿塊抹布給我，讓我擦一下眼睛。天啊。
get a rag and wipe Sacrifice Samuel out my damn eye. OMG.
嘿。
Hey.
不錯，約翰。
Nice one, John.
噢，我的天。
[gasps] Oh, my God.
我身上也已經弄髒了
I've got Sacrifice Samuel all over me.
這盒子裏是什麼？
What's in the box?
那麼，蜜蜂，如果你已經知道該怎麼做了，你為什麼還需要這本書？
Yo, so, Bee, why do you need the book if you already know what to do?
這就像耶穌向天堂問路。
It's like Jesus asking directions to heaven.
去他媽的上去，你知道嗎？
Just fucking go up, you know?
猶太人有卷軸。
Well, the Jews have their scrolls,
基督徒有他們的聖經。
Christians have their Bibles,
魔鬼也有他的詩句。
and the devil has his verses.
別碰它。它非常古老，非常精緻。
Don't touch it. It's very old and very delicate.
這是唯一的一本。
It's the only one.
血流到頁面時，你背誦這首詩。
You recite the verse while the blood hits the page.
沒有它，這一切都不會實現
Without it, none of this happens.
在我們上樓去幹掉那小孩，取無辜的血之前，讓我們開始吧。
Let's get started before we head upstairs and get the blood of the innocent.
911，你有什麼緊急情況？
[woman] 911, what's your emergency?
我叫科爾·詹森。一個人在我的客廳被殺了。
My name is Cole Johnson. A guy was murdered in my living room.
地址是呃..。大比道2455號。
The address is, uh... 2455 Bigby Drive.
-你能派人來嗎？-殺人者還在房子裏嗎？
-Can you please send someone? - Are the attackers still in the house?
他們在樓下玩爆了。
They're downstairs having a blast.
-有多少人，科爾？-太多了.。
- How many are there, Cole? -Too many.
你能把我媽媽找來嗎？她在城裏的凱悅酒店。
Can you please get my mom? She's at the Hyatt in the city.
大酒店
Living large.
當然，科爾，現在聽我說。重要的是你要躲起來。
Of course, Cole. Now listen to me. It's important that you stay hidden.
-我要保護自己.。謝謝。-別這樣做。不，不，不-。
-I gotta protect myself. Thanks. -Do not do that. No, no, no--
-好吧.。
-Okay. -[chattering]
...我們的死亡細胞約有15%脫落。
[Bee] ...we shed about 15 percent of our dead cells.
哇！
[John] Whoo!
喲，這孩子的嗜好，就是喜歡被別人欺負。
Yo, this kid's hobby must be getting bullied.
他在讀“秘密”這本書？
He's reading The Secret?
他十歲了。他需要知道什麼秘密？
He's ten years old. What secret he need to know?
他不會聽見我們說話嗎？
Won't he hear us?
媽的，當然不會，我給他喝了酒還下了藥。
With the amount of drugs I gave him? Hell, no.
- 好孩子。帥哥。-你有針嗎？
-[Sonya] Good boy. Pretty boy. -Do you have the needle?
當然，我有針。
Of course, I have the needle.
有一種更快的方法來獲取所有的血。
You know, there is a faster way to get all that blood.
如果把他殺了會發生什麼事情？
[Bee] What happens when you kill someone?
他們失去了所有的Instagram粉絲。
[John] They lose, like, all they Instagram followers.
-天啊，那太糟糕了。-不，如果他們死了。
-[gasps] Oh, my God, that would suck. -No, they die.
我就得再找一個無辜的孩子。
And then I'd have to find another innocent kid.
而我們必須找到所有奇怪的血液混合在一起才能夠奏效。
And all of this only works if we get that top-shelf pure shit.
科爾基的血本上是我們的水龍頭，源源不斷。
And Cole is basically a faucet of that for us.
在這之後，我們完成儀式..。
[Bee] After this, we finish the ritual...
而你的願望實現了。
and your wish comes true.
-該死，我錯過了靜脈。- 嗯。
-Damn, I missed the vein. -[Sonya] Mm.
勇敢點兒。
[Bee] Premium real estate. Go for it.
等等，你得給他幫個忙.。
Wait, you gotta give him a Band-Aid.
好的，我們去把血液混合吧。
Okay. Let's go mix some blood.
約翰，胡說。
John, alley-oop.
勒布朗·詹姆斯。
[John] LeBron James.
真是好孩子。
Good boy.
他為什麼光著身子？
Why is he shirtless?
-這是你的第一個問題？-你怎麼能問這個？看看他。
-That's your first question? -How can you ask that? Just look at him.
我還是不明白。
I still don't get it.
給他一塊餅乾。
Give him a cookie.
-不用了，謝謝。-吃餅乾。
-No, thanks. -Eat the cookie.
我只是不太喜歡餅乾，好嗎？蜜蜂知道。
I just don't really like cookies, okay? Bee knows that.
如果你吃東西，你會感覺好些的。暈過去了。
You'll feel better if you eat. You fainted.
不，我沒有。
No, I didn't.
是的，你有。
Yes, you did.
在我取了你的血之後。
After I took your blood,
我在房間裏等著，因為感覺到不對
I waited in the room, because something felt off.
所以我蹲在門後。幾秒鐘後，你起床了。
I crouched behind the door. A few seconds later, you got up,
把床單綁在床上，把床單扔出窗外。
tied a sheet to your bed, threw the sheet out the window.
然後你暈倒了。所以，你知道..。
And then you fainted. So, you know...
你的血糖很低。吃餅乾。
Your blood sugar is low. Eat the cookie.
你生我氣了嗎？
Are you mad at me?
吃餅乾。
Cookie.
一定會很好吃的。
This is gonna be so good.
搞什麼..。
What the...
哦，給你。
Oh, there you go.
就這樣。
There you go.
一個好孩子。
That's a good boy.
-你為什麼醒著，科爾？-因為我睡不著。
-Why are you awake, Cole? -Because I couldn't sleep.
-我不相信你。- 好的，好的。I-。
-I don't believe you. -[Cole] Okay, fine. I--
我要去樹林裏抽煙。
I was gonna go smoke in the woods.
你本來要在樹林裏抽煙的。
[Bee] You were gonna go smoke in the woods.
是的，你知道，就像...大麻。
Yeah. You know, like... marijuana.
你不打算和拿出來分享嗎？來吧，夥計。
You weren't gonna share with your boy? Come on, man.
聽我的混音磁帶，我們本來可以興奮到很嗨的！
We could've got high, listen to my mix tape. My shit's fire.
-我要抽大麻.。-你為什麼沒喝我給你的酒？
-I wanna smoke pot. -Why didn't you drink the shot?
他為什麼光著身子？你為什麼要取我的血？
Why is he shirtless? Why did you take my blood?
科爾-好吧，因為我不喜歡喝酒。
-Cole. -Okay. Fine. Because I don't like alcohol.
因為我想讓你覺得我很酷。
I just drank it because I wanted you to think I was cool.
你為什麼要給一個12歲的孩子喝酒？
Why did you give a 12-year-old alcohol?
因為我在酒裏放了迷藥，可以讓你睡上八個小時以上。
'Cause I put shit in that alcohol that makes them conk out
八個小時以上。
for eight hours or more.
你還看到了什麼？
What else did you see?
我剛見到你。
I just see you.
還有這些不認識的混蛋，在我家。
And these assholes, who I don't know, in my house.
-為什麼他的襯衫上沾滿了血？-沒人會讓我借襯衫給他了。
-Why is his shirt covered in blood? -No one would let me borrow a shirt.
-那甚至不是答案。-天哪.。
-That's not even an answer. -Oh, my God.
難道他沒有看到他身後的鏡子嗎？我們可以看到你在割斷繩子。
Does he not see the mirror behind him? We can see you cutting the rope.
他現在知道了。
Well, he does now.
太可愛了，你還在割斷繩子。
Aw, it's so cute, you're still cutting the rope.
看看你。你真的在努力，不是嗎？
Look at you. You're really trying there, aren't you?
-你為什麼要割斷繩索？-我不喜歡被綁起來。
-Why are you cutting ropes? -I don't like being tied up.
-你為什麼帶刀？-這是禮物.。
-Why do you have a knife? -It was a gift.
天哪。
Oh, my God.
他還在割斷繩索。
He's still cutting the ropes.
好堅決的小混蛋，不是嗎？
Determined little fucker, aren't you?
聽著，我不會告訴任何人。
Look, I won't tell anyone.
好吧。你瞭解我。我很保守秘密的。
Okay? You know me. I'm good with secrets.
我不會告訴我父母你在狂歡
I won't tell my parents that you were having an orgy
需要我的血來做。
and needed my blood to do it.
你知道什麼是狂歡嗎？
Do you even know what an orgy is?
我猜這是可悲之人做的可悲之事。
I'm guessing it's something sad people do
因為他們想讓其他可悲的人喜歡他們。
'cause they want other sad people to like them,
他們在一起的時候，可以忘記這些可悲的事情，哪怕是一分鐘。
and they can forget for one minute how sad they are in general.
事實上，這是一個相當好的答案。
That's actually a pretty good answer.
是為了一個科學專案好嗎？
It was for a science project, okay?
狂歡？
The orgy?
不是，是因為血。
No. The blood.
狂歡是一群人在一起做愛的時候。
Orgy is when a bunch of people have sex together.
我們不需要你的血。
We wouldn't need your blood for that.
你本可以直接問的。
You could've just asked.
我會為了你，為了科學而獻血的。
I would've let you have some blood for science.
我知道你害怕針頭。
I knew you were afraid of needles.
這顯然是個誤會。
This was clearly a misunderstanding.
索尼婭解開他。
Sonya, untie him.
對不起，我們嚇到你了，科爾，沒事吧？
I'm sorry we scared you, Cole. We good?
- 噢，該死。
-[John] Oh, shit. -[screaming]
- 閉嘴！-媽的！
-[Max] Shut up! -Holy fuck!
-不好.。-該死的員警。
-Not good. -Fucking police.
員警為什麼在外面，科爾？
Why are the cops outside, Cole?
-我不知道。-你給他們打電話了嗎？
-I don't know. -Did you call them?
-不是。你說你在房間裏。-讓我覺得你看到了什麼。
-No. You said you were in the room. -Makes me think you saw something
嚇得你要報警。科爾？
that scared you enough to call the cops. Right, Cole?
-噢，操！
-[knock on door] -Oh, fuck!
回答我，科爾。
Answer me, Cole.
噢。
[grunts] Ow.
-哦，該死！- 各位，別動！
-Oh, shit! -[officer] Everybody, freeze!
舉起手來，馬上！舉起手來！馬上！
[officer 2] Hands up, now! Put your hands up! Now!
-馬上！- 我們開始行動。
-Now! -[Max] Here we go.
舉起手來！- 哦！
-[officer] Hands up! -[John] Oh!
該死！
-[chuckles] -[officer] Shit!
舉起手來。別開槍，夥計。黑人的生命也很重要。感覺到我了嗎？
Hands up. Don't shoot, man. Black lives matter, too. You feel me?
蜜蜂！
[Allison] Bee!
-哦！- 哦，該死！
-Oh! -[Max] Oh, shit!
泰蒂死了！
Titty gone!
別動。舉起你的手。不許動！
Don't you move. Keep your hands up. Nobody move!
-你別動。
-[screams] -Don't you move.
拿槍的，你給我冷靜點！
[John] Chill with the gun stuff.
冷靜，你是墨西哥人對吧？聽著，我會說水療-。
Chill. You Mexican, right? Look, I speak Spa--
羅森托，我的黑鬼，羅森托。
Lo siento , my nigga, lo siento.
-你是認真的嗎？-
-Are you serious? -[laughing]
麥克斯，你在幹什麼，夥計？
[John] Max, what you doing, man?
麥克斯，你在幹什麼，夥計？-不，不，不！
-[John] Max, what you doing, man? -No, no, no!
-哦。
-[officer 2 shouting] -Oh.
不！
No!
用力點。
Harder.
哇！
Whoo!
聽著，夥計。四分之三的人得了性病。
Look, man. Three out of four people got an STD.
我身上有兩個人的血。
I got two people's blood on me.
算一算。我得了愛滋病。我知道我得了愛滋病。
You do the math. I got AIDS. I know I got AIDS.
是你殺了他！
You killed him!
-這是你的錯，兄弟.。-你瘋了嗎？
-Kind of your fault, bud. -Are you insane?
不，科爾，我只是...。
No, Cole. I'm just trying--
在大比大道的187呼叫的情況如何？
[man on radio] What's the status of that 187 call on Bigby Drive?
聽著，夥計。
[John] Look, man.
我不能進監獄。你們都殺了員警。
I can't go to jail. Y'all killed the cops, man.
我沒有參與這件事。
I ain't involved with this shit.
沒事的。麥克斯，拿起來。
It's fine. Max, pick it up.
這是統計數字。
[John] It's the statistics.
據說你要麼進了監獄要麼死了。
They say you either end up in jail or dead.
都是為了我，比。
It's gonna be both for me, Bee.
-“完全清除”的暗碼應該怎麼說？- 你的狀況如何？
-What's the code for "all clear"? -[man] What's your status?
說“安全”就行了。
Just say "all clear."
他為什麼要知道員警的暗碼？
[Sonya] Why would he know cop codes?
別尖叫了，你要表現得像個成年人。
Stop screaming and act like an adult.
暗碼是什麼？我知道你知道的。
What's the code? I know you know it.
這裏的小男孩是個書呆子。告訴他們暗碼。
Little boy here a nerd. Tell them the codes.
暗碼是什麼？
What's the code?
-十，五，十三。- 趕緊輸入這些數字。
-Ten-fifty-three. -[John] Punch that shit in.
拜納克，你在嗎？-等等.。
-[man] Bynak, you there? -Wait.
你難道不明白。你在撒謊的時候，你會把目光移開。
[Bee] You don't get it. You look away when you lie.
你看著我的眼睛，告訴我真的暗碼。
You look me in the eyes and tell me the truth.
“全部清除”的暗碼是什麼？
What is the code for "all clear"?
是10-4。很明顯。
It's 10-4. Obviously.
什麼是“我們休息一下，吃點東西”？
What's "we're taking a break to get food"?
說我們休息一下-
-[Cole] Say we're taking a break to-- -[Bee] Cole.
拜納克警官你需要支援嗎？
[man] Officer Bynak, you need backup?
暗碼七。
Code seven.
十，四，安全.。我們是七。
Ten-four, all clear. We're code seven.
十，四。你們兩個慢慢享受！
[man] Ten-four. Enjoy your double-double.
應該搞定了。
Should've been a cop.
他媽的。
Shit.
噢，噢！
[groaning] Ow, ow!
哦，天啊，夥計們。
[Allison] Oh, my God. Guys.
天哪。
Oh, my God!
他媽的趕緊過來幫我。你幹嗎呢?
Fucking help me. What are you doing?
天啊，他朝我胸部開槍了。
Oh, my God. He shot me in the boob.
什麼樣的老二會朝一個女孩的胸部開槍？
What kind of dick shoots a girl in the boob?
-我沒有報名參加這個活動.。-別抱怨了.。別再抱怨了。
-I did not sign up for this shit. -Stop complaining. Stop all your whining.
它們還沒有發育完全呢，這回要停止繼續生長了。
They're totally gonna stop growing. They weren't even done.
有時候你必須冷靜下來好嗎？
Sometimes you gotta settle, all right?
我有個表妹，錢特爾，奶子平了。
I got a cousin Chantelle, titties flat.
還不是活的很好。
Personality real good.
哦，我的天。
Ow. Oh, my God.
-噢！該死的賤人。
-Ow! You fucking bitch. -[Sonya laughs]
你怎麼啦?
What's wrong with you?
-帶著你那該死的貝雷帽離我遠點.。-她會流血的。
-Get away from me with your fucking beret. -She's gonna bleed out.
怎麼啦? 不。
What? No.
什麼意思，我要一直流血嗎？
What do you mean, I'm gonna bleed?
我們能不能把衛生棉什麼的塞進去？
Can we just stick a tampon in it or something?
天啊，我們得叫救護車了，夥計們。
Oh, my God. We need to call an ambulance, guys.
我要輛救護車。我不想失去我的胸部。
I need an ambulance. I don't wanna lose my boob.
我不能那樣做。
I can't do that.
什麼？
[Allison] What?
為什麼不行?。
Why not?
因為你的胸部是被一個現在已經死了的員警擊中的。
Because your boob was shot by a now-dead cop.
你怎麼跟人解釋這一點？
Have fun explaining that.
沒有人會喜歡沒有胸的女人的，蜜蜂。
No dude's gonna motorboat these, Bee.
你喜歡嗎？你想要它們晃的快一些，還是想要它們大一些？
How you like it? You want them quick or you want them long?
你想吐點唾沫在它們上面？
[continues mimicking motorboat] You want a little spit on them?
科爾！
[Bee] Cole!
天啊 嘿，嘿，嘿。
-[Allison] Oh, my God. -[John] Hey, hey, hey.
誰會想吸我的乳頭？
Who's gonna want to suck on my nipples?
沒有人
No one.
科爾，過來，科爾，別跑了。
[John] Cole. Come here, Cole. Stop running.
過來，小寶貝。過來夥計。
Come here, little baby. Yeah. Come here, buddy.
只是想談談。只是想談談。
Just wanna talk. Just wanna talk.
狗養的。
Son of a bitch.
嘿，這裏不是你一個人的家。嘿，嘿，嘿。
Hey, this ain't Home Alone. Hey, hey, hey.
噢，該死。
Oh, shit.
右頸靜脈。耶。
Right in the jugular. Yeah! [chuckles]
-抓住他。-我要抓到他了。
-Get him. -I got him.
我要赤手空拳殺了你。
I'm gonna kill you with my bare hands.
哇！
Whoo!
-現在我得收拾乾淨了.。- 快跑，科爾！
-Now I gotta clean this up. -[Max] Run, Cole!
我來找你了。
I'm coming for you.
開門，科爾。
Open the door, Cole.
沒有鎖上的門，科爾！
No locked doors, Cole!
開門！我們只想談談科爾。
Open the door. We just wanna talk, Cole.
來吧，科爾！
Come on, Cole!
科利。掛得怎麼樣？
Hey, Coley. How's it hanging?
拜託，別殺我。求你了。
Please, don't kill me. Please.
不，你會殺了我的。不。
No. You're gonna kill me. No.
麥克斯，沒事的，麥克斯，拜託。
Max. It's okay, Max. Please.
抓住你了。
Got you.
哇！
Ow!
深呼吸夥計。
Whoa. Deep breaths, buddy.
我就在你屁股上，科利！
[Max] I'm right on your ass, Coley!
繼續前進！
Keep moving!
來吧，科爾！
Come on, Cole!
你在哪，你這個小混蛋？
Where are you, you little shit?
科爾。
Cole.
科利。
Coley.
有個死人...。
There's a dead guy...
對不起。
I'm sorry.
好的，好的，好的。
Okay. Okay. Okay.
噴霧劑。毯子。
Bug spray. Blanket.
打火機。
Lighter.
哇，肥龍。
Whoa. The Fat Dragon.
科利！
[Max] Coley!
科爾！
Cole!
出來玩吧！
Come out and play!
[索尼婭耳語道：“你就在這裏嗎？”
[Sonya whispers] Is this where you are?
你說得對...在這裏嗎？
Are you right... here?
真是好孩子。
Good boy.
帥哥。
Beautiful boy.
那麼柔軟，那麼漂亮。
So soft, so pretty.
科利！
[Max] Coley!
-科爾在哪？- 啊。
-Where's Cole? -[Sonya] Ugh.
索尼婭，把你的餅乾拿來，幫我找到這個小混蛋。
[Max] Sonya, bring your cookies and help me find this little fuck.
我來了。
[Sonya] I'm coming.
科爾你好。
Hi, Cole.
啊呀，天啊，真糟。
Oh, God.
你覺得你父母要花多長時間？
How long do you think it'll take your parents
找到你的屍體？
to find your body down here? [chuckles]
明天？
Tomorrow?
兩天后？
Two days from now?
以後呢？
Even later?
可能當你的身體開始散發出乳酪的臭味。
Probably when your body starts to reek like cheese.
或者我們可以把你的身體燒了，科爾。
[laughs] Or we could just burn your body, Cole.
會很漂亮的。
It would be so beautiful.
哦，你打偏了。
[laughs] Oh, you missed.
我的指甲！
My nails!
科爾！科爾！
Cole! Cole! [grunts]
科爾，我要在你死之前折磨你
I'm gonna make sure you hurt before you die, Cole.
切斷你的手指。每一根
Cut your fingers off. Every single one.
過來，科爾！
Come here, Cole!
我要把你作為這些蜈蚣蜘蛛大餐。嗯。
I'm making a human self-centipede. Yeah!
人類蜘蛛蜈蚣大餐，孩子！
Human self-centipede, child!
會很好吃的，科爾！
Gonna taste so good, Cole!
科爾，你的嘴會被縫在屁股上的！
Your mouth is gonna get sewn to your ass, Cole!
你的臭屁股！
Your mouthy ass!
-我還活著，媽的-。
I'm still alive motherfuck--
你剛才炸了索尼婭嗎？
Did you just blow up Sonya?
沒有。
No.
我的意思是，我甚至沒有生氣。我有點驚訝。
I mean, I'm not even mad. I'm a little surprised.
怎麼回事？
What did that?
一個煙火。
A firework.
一個煙火？
A firework?
天啊。
Holy shit.
該死，你很厲害，孩子。
Damn, good for you, kid.
太棒了。
That is awesome.
所以，現在可以開始了嗎？
So, you want a head start?
-拜託，你是四分衛。-生活是不公平的，夥計。
-Come on, you're the quarterback. -Life's not fair, dude.
你們真不要臉。
You guys suck.
你剛剛炸了索尼婭。
You just blew up Sonya.
科爾，你不能超過我。
You can't outrun me, Cole.
等到他們快抓到你了，像一袋石頭一樣倒下去。
Wait until they've almost got you, drop like a bag of rocks.
踢他的雞巴。
[Bee] Kick him in the dick.
踢他。
Dick.
哇！
Whoo!
你竟然踢我的老二。
You missed my dick.
-不，我沒有。-很確定你做了.。
-No, I didn't. -Pretty sure you did.
還有個大雞巴。
And I got a big dick.
不，你沒有。
No, you don't.
這太傷人了。
That's just hurtful.
拜託，別...別...。
Please, don't-- Don't--
沒有抱怨。
[Max] No whining.
保留一些尊嚴。
Save some dignity.
【雞蛋打破的聲音】。
[egg breaking]
-那是什麼鬼聲音？-
-What the hell is that? -[gasping]
-嗯？-是傑瑞米。
-Huh? -It's Jeremy.
-什麼？-雞蛋。
-What? -Eggs.
雞蛋。
Eggs.
雞蛋？
Eggs?
你一定在騙我。
You gotta be shitting me.
有人在砸你的房子？
Somebody's egging your house?
這孩子是誰？
[Max] Who is this kid?
一個混蛋而已。
Just an asshole.
-他經常用雞蛋砸你的房子？-有時候.。
-He egg your house a lot? -Sometimes.
- 那麼，你打算怎麼做呢？-什麼？
-[Max] So, what are you gonna do about it? -What?
我說，你要讓那個小流氓到你的房子裏來撒野嗎？
I said, are you gonna let that little punk come on to your property？
不尊重你的家庭財產，不尊重你？
your family's property and disrespect you like that?
不，該死，不，這是美國。你得去教訓他。
No. Hell, no. This is America. You need to wreck his ass.
你在開我的玩笑嗎？
Are you kidding me?
出去把那個賤人打一頓。
Get out there and crush that bitch.
上啊。
Go.
喔 喔 喔。
[chuckles] Well, well, well.
是科爾。
It's Cole sore.
我喜歡你的睡衣。
I like your pajamas.
-謝謝.。是我媽媽做的。-
-Thanks. My mom made them. -[scoffs]
你想怎樣？
You wanna do something?
知道我要幹什麼嗎？
You know what I'm gonna do?
你想幹什麼?。
What's that?
我要用這個右腳。
I'm gonna take this right foot,
而我要在你的臉的那一邊打你。
and I'm gonna whop you on that side of your face.
而且你對此也無能為力。
And there's not a damn thing you can do about it.
真的嗎？
[chuckles] Really?
真的。
Really.
我要毀了你的屁股。
I'm gonna wreck your ass.
那到底是什麼鬼啊？你他媽的肯定是瘋了。
What the hell was that? You must be crazy.
傑瑞米你得聽我說好嗎。
Jeremy, you have to listen to me, okay?
那邊有個人想殺我。
There's a guy over there who's trying to kill me.
我對天發誓-我對天發誓。
-I swear to God. -I swear to God.
-我是認真的.。-我是認真的.。
-I'm serious. -I'm serious.
我家有屍體。
There are dead bodies in my house.
-等等，真的嗎？-員警來了.。他們殺了員警。
-Wait, seriously? -The cops came. They killed the cops.
-警車在哪里？-他們瘋了，他們把他們藏起來了。
-Where is the cop car? -They're crazy. They're covering it up.
好吧。如果你能幫我，我就戴上藍色的頭巾。
Okay? If you get me out of this, I'll wear a blue headband.
我給你做足部按摩。到大學為止，我會做你的家庭作業。
I'll give you foot massages. I'll do your homework until college.
哦，好的，好的。
Oh, okay, okay.
我來幫你。
I'll help you.
-真的嗎？-是的.。
-Really? -Yeah.
如果你死了我還能夠找誰欺負？
I mean, if you die, who am I gonna pick on?
一點兒沒錯。
Exactly.
好的，這是計畫。
Okay, so, here's the plan.
我數到三，我們就趕緊跑，跑到我的自行車那裏。
On three, we're gonna make a run for my bike.
-你坐後座。明白了。-謝謝.。
-You're gonna ride in the back. All right? -Thank you.
一，二-。
One, two--
很高興被我騙了！
Have fun getting murdered, colon cancer.
哇，哇-哇.。
Ooh-whah, ooh-whah.
你說的太多了。
You talk too much.
下次直接打他的臉。
Crack him in the face next time.
不過還不錯。至少你是為自己站出來的。
Not bad. At least you stood up for yourself.
你現在就放我走？
You gonna let me go now?
不。
No.
但如果你殺了我，你就得不到你想要的。
But if you kill me, you won't get what you want.
不，我和其他人不一樣。
No, I'm not like the others.
我是來殺人的。
I came here to kill people.
對。科爾，這就是我要說的！
Yes! That's what I'm talking about, Cole!
快點，夥計！哇！
Come on, buddy! Whoo!
來吧，科利。
Come on, Coley.
來吧，夥計。我就在你後面。滾開，科爾。
Come on, buddy. I'm right behind you. Move your ass, Cole.
哇！
Whoo!
來找你了。
Coming for you.
-哇！
-[Cole screams] -Whoo!
來吧，夥計。快動起來。
Come on, buddy. Get moving.
來吧，夥計。
Come on, buddy.
來吧！
Let's go!
來吧(趕快)。上去！來吧(趕快)。
Come on! Get up there! Come on!
科利。
[singsong] Coley.
下來玩吧。
Come down and play.
科利。
Coley.
來吧，科爾。
Come on, Cole.
噓 噓 噓，啊。
Chi-chi-chi, chi-chi-chi, ah
被困在樹上。
Stuck in the tree.
不能下去！
No way down!
科利。
Coley.
他在哪里？
[gasping] Where is he?
你是個壞孩子。
[in normal voice] You're a badass kid.
放鬆，麥克斯。
Relax, Max.
你不必這樣做。
You don't have to do this.
嗯，我一定要這麼做。
Well, I kind of have to do this.
別擔心。我不會讓你死的時候臉上還帶著雞蛋。
Don't worry. I'm not gonna let you die with egg on your face.
可憐的混蛋。
You poor bastard.
你應該得到比這更好的結果。
You deserve better than this.
今晚你會死的很光彩。
Tonight you get an honorable death.
今晚你就死定了。
Tonight you die a man.
我不想死得像個男人。
I don't wanna die a man.
為什麼會有槍？
Why are there guns?
到這兒來。到這兒來。
Come here. Come here.
-那是把槍嗎？-有兩個男人和一個亞洲女孩。
-Was that a gun? -I got the two guys and the Asian girl.
-啦啦隊長中槍了。是蜜蜂幹的。-發生了什麼事？
-The cheerleader got shot. It's just Bee. -What is going on?
蜜蜂殺了那個怪人。偷了我的血。把我綁起來。殺了員警。
Bee murdered the geek. Stole my blood. Tied me up. Killed the cops.
-你真把我嚇壞了。-不好意思...。
-You're really freaking me out. -I'm... sorry.
蜜蜂是壞的？
Bee is bad?
是的，蜜蜂很壞。
Yeah. Bee is bad.
-你爸爸在哪？-和一些人鬼混去了。
-Where's your dad? -Out with some Protestant.
-但他的車在這兒。-她把他抱起來了。他真的很絕望。
-But his car's here. -She picked him up. He's really desperate.
難道只有我還有保姆嗎？
Am I the only one that still has a babysitter?
嗯。
Yeah.
-那我們怎麼辦？-求你了。
-So, what do we do? -Pray.
-好的.。-我開玩笑的.。
-Okay. -I was kidding.
-哦.。-不過這可能是個好主意.。
-Oh. -But it's probably a great idea, though.
快。
Come on.
-你覺得她能進來嗎？-如果鎖上了就不行。
-You think she can get in here? -Not if it's locked.
你的門是自動鎖的，對吧？
[Cole] Your door automatically locks, right?
不。
[Melanie] Nope.
-我不該讓你捲入這件事。-你被槍擊了。
-I shouldn't have gotten you into this. -You were being shot at.
就是因為我被槍擊了。
Especially because I was being shot at.
很抱歉，你是我最好的朋友。這事我會處理好的。
You're my best friend, I'm sorry. I'm gonna take care of this.
-你有手機嗎？-是的.。
-Do you have your phone? -Yeah.
-叫員警。告訴他們是10-53。-你為什麼知道員警的暗碼？
-Call the cops. Tell them it's a 10-53. -Why do you know cop codes?
因為我長大後就想當員警了。
Because I used to wanna be a cop when I grew up.
你從沒有告訴過我。
You never told me that.
我知道呀。我只告訴了比。
I know. I only told Bee.
【塵土飛揚的斯普林菲爾德的“幽靈”演奏】。
[Dusty Springfield's "Spooky" playing]
你沒事吧?。
Are you okay?
我過了一個非常糟糕的夜晚。
I've had a really bad night.
♪然後我停下來♪
♪ And then I stop ♪
♪然後說“好吧”♪
♪ And say "all right" ♪
♪和像你這樣一個恐怖的小男孩戀愛有點瘋狂♪
♪ Love is kind of crazy With a spooky little boy like you ♪
最後一個被吻的人被兩把刀刺中頭部。
Uh... The last guy I saw get kissed got stabbed in the head by two knives.
♪一直讓我猜♪
♪ You always keep me guessing ♪
♪我似乎從來不知道你在想什麼♪
♪ I never seem to know What you're thinking ♪
僅僅因為她是個精神病患者並不意味著女人是邪惡的。
Just because she's a psychopath doesn't mean women are evil.
我知道這點。
I know that.
真希望所有的女孩都像你一樣。
I wish all girls were like you.
♪然後你笑了♪
♪ And then you smile ♪
我要結束這一切。
I'm gonna put an end to this.
你幹嗎呢?
What are you doing?
-保護你的安全.。-鎖在裏面，笨蛋。
-Keeping you safe. -The lock is on the inside, dumbass.
你真是太好了。
That was sweet of you.
我真的很興奮我們接吻了。
I'm really excited we kissed.
我也是。下次我們親熱吧。
Me, too. Let's make out next time.
好的，再見。
Okay. Bye.
過來抓我，蜜蜂！
Come and get me, Bee!
我就在這兒！
I'm right here!
只有你和我！
It's just you and me!
什麼，你現在要害羞了？
What, you're gonna get shy now?
我要回家去！
I'm going towards my house!
蜜蜂，我就在這裏！
I'm right here, Bee!
我就在這兒！
I'm right here!
神馬東西。
What the hell?
天哪，屍體都去哪里了？
Oh, my God. Where is everything?
天哪。
Oh, my God.
“犧牲...。實現你的夢想...“。
"Sacrifice... Get your dreams..."
-放開我！-我要殺了你！
-Get off me! -I'm gonna kill you!
我要殺了你！
I'm gonna kill you!
天哪。
Oh, my God!
你怎麼了，小變態？
What's wrong with you, you little pervert?
什麼?你在攻擊我，我這是在自衛，保護自己。
What? You can't make me feel bad because I defended myself.
我知道你一直都想讓我在樓上你的小房間裏。
I knew you wanted me this whole time, upstairs in your little room jerking off.
-你只是病了。-你是想殺我.。
-You're just sick. -You were trying to kill me.
我不是想通過打你的雞巴來殺你。
I wasn't trying to kill you by punching your dick.
我從來沒有感覺到如此被侵犯過。
[shouts] I've never felt so violated before.
啊呀，天啊，真糟。
Oh, God.
我只是報名參加了這個愚蠢的活動，這樣我就能找到我理想的工作了。
I only signed up for this dumb shit so I could have my dream job.
相反，我現在有什麼，嗯？
And instead, what do I have now, huh?
這個。
This.
有一個乾癟醜陋的胸部。
One deflated, ugly boob. [scoffs]
我以後的生活基本上沒戲了。
[sobbing] My life is basically over.
我--我是說...你還是超級性感。
I-- I mean... you're still super hot.
你想要什麼樣的工作？
What kind of job do you want?
記者。
Journalist.
看，那太完美了。
See, that's perfect.
因為你超聰明而且很性感。
Because you're super smart, and you're hot,
-而且真的很有動力.。-謝謝.。
-and really driven. -Thank you.
我可能錯了，但我認為這對你來說並不難。
I could be wrong, but I don't think it would be hard for you
過你想要的生活。
to have a cool life.
真的?。
Really?
你想會是這樣嗎？你覺得我們能擺脫這一切？
You think so? You think maybe we could walk out of this whole thing?
叫員警就好，你知道，忘記這一切嗎？
Just call the police and just, you know, forget this ever happened?
嗯。
Yeah.
一點兒沒錯。
Exactly.
你覺得我會管你在說什麼嗎？
Do you think I give a fuck what you're talking about?
小刀。刀在哪里？
[Cole] Knife. Where's the knife?
哦！洗碗機。
Oh! Dishwasher.
媽媽。
Mom.
是你把刀放在洗碗機裏的嗎？
Are you the one that put the knife in the dishwasher?
我也這麼想。
I think so.
你能不這麼做嗎？你應該放在切菜的那邊。
Can you not do that? It goes in the butcher block.
呦呼！
Yoo-hoo!
我找到這個？
Looking for this?
你還覺得我漂亮嗎？
You still think I'm pretty?
噢，你覺得我怕火嗎？
Oh, you think I'm scared of a little fire, huh?
你快死了。
You are dying.
你，你快死了。
You, you are dying.
你把我的人生都毀了。
You ruined my life.
現在，我要毀了你的！
And now, I'm gonna ruin yours!
天啊。
Holy shit.
在警車裏發現的。太厲害了。
I found this in the cop car. That was so graphic.
她真煩人。
She was so annoying.
我想吐了。
I wanna throw up.
你與我都一樣。
You and me both.
索尼婭在哪兒？
Where's Sonya?
炸死了！在樓板下麵，員警的屍體在哪里？
Blown up. Crawlspace. Where are the cops?
用車把他們給甩屍了。
Ditched them with the car.
現在我又要蹺課了。
Now I gotta skip town again.
剩下的就是你，還有你該怎麼辦。
And that leaves you, and what to do with you.
-有什麼建議嗎？-你要開槍打我嗎？
-Any suggestions? -Are you gonna shoot me?
不。
No.
不，我只是在你身邊開槍，因為我以為你會舉起手來。
No. I was just shooting around you, 'cause I thought you'd put your hands up.
我要燒掉你的書！
I will burn your book!
科爾。
Cole.
-科爾，聽我說。-不。
-Cole, listen to me. -No.
-科爾，聽我說。-不，蜜蜂！你給我聽仔細了。
-Cole, listen to me. -No, Bee! You listen to me!
我被你們追著砍殺，你偷了我的血，殺了人。
I've been hunted, you've stolen my blood, killed people,
朝我開槍，整晚都是個混蛋將軍。
shot at me, and just been general assholes all night.
所以，我想知道到底發生了什麼。
So, I wanna know what the hell's going on.
科爾，你太年輕了，不明白，好嗎？相信我就好。
Cole, you're too young to understand, okay? Just trust me.
你這混蛋。
Fuck you!
科爾。
Cole.
不，你知道嗎？那是你應得的。
No. You know what? You deserved that.
什麼，就因為我12歲，就意味著我會被像欺負，被侮辱。
What, just because I'm 12 means I get to be treated like total shit
和其他人一樣？
by you and Jeremy and everyone else?
你猜怎麼著?你是廣告狂人的唐.德雷珀。
You know what? You're Don Draper from Mad Men.
他是多麼酷，多麼英俊，每個人都愛他，
How he's all cool and handsome and everybody loves him,
然後他回家，你發現他一直都有妻子。
then he goes home and you find out he has a wife the whole time.
-他真是個混蛋！-你是為了我毀了廣告狂人嗎？
-He's such a piece of shit! -Did you just ruin Mad Men for me?
它甚至不再播放了。你會活下來的。
It's not even on anymore. You'll live.
還是。
Still.
-當你離開這裏時會發生什麼？-什麼意思？
-What happens when you leave here? -What do you mean?
-我要燒掉這個！-好吧。
-I will burn this! -Okay.
科爾...你想知道什麼？
Cole... what do you want to know?
血液是幹什麼用的？
What's the blood for?
你把無辜的血和犧牲的人的血混在一起，
You mix the blood of the innocent with the blood of someone sacrificed,
然後背誦咒語，
recite the verses,
把它滴在紙上。
while dripping it on the page.
基本上，你想要什麼就得到什麼。
And, basically, you get whatever you want.
過去我很膽小...很害怕。
I used to be so small... and so scared.
現在我很堅強...而且我有信心..。
Now I'm strong... and I'm confident...
這就是我所想要的。
and that's all I ever wanted.
所以，對你來說
And, so, that's all I was to you.
只是利用我來得到你想要的。
You just used me to get what you wanted.
不。
No.
不，科爾，我選了你。
No, Cole. I chose you.
我是說，我本可以殺了你，而不是愛麗森。
I mean, I could've shot you and not Allison,
但我沒有。選擇了你。
but I didn't. I chose you.
因為你是最棒的。
'Cause you're the best.
對吧？你是我的人。
We click, right? You're my guy.
我不是第一個孩子，是嗎？
I'm not the first kid, am I?
不。
No.
然後你就離開這裏，找到另一個水龍頭。
And you'll leave here and just find another faucet.
-你聽到了？-我什麼都聽到了.。這是我的房子。
-You heard that? -I heard everything. This is my house.
好吧。
Okay.
好的，是的。
Okay, yes.
今晚糟透了但我們可以重新開始。
And tonight sucked, but we can start again.
那麼你有計劃？
So, you have a plan?
是的，我們只是說他們襲擊了我們。
Yeah. We just say they attacked us.
找到他了。
I got him.
哇！
Whoo!
而且，夥計，我們會很開心的。
Plus, dude, we would have so much fun.
只有你和我對抗整個世界。
Just you and me against the whole world.
再也不會有人傷害你了。
No one will ever hurt you ever again.
就沒有什麼好害怕的了。這不是你想要的嗎？
There'll be nothing left to be afraid of. Isn't that what you wanted?
科爾，你說呢？
What do you say, Cole?
我猜..。
I guess...
我想我也有個計畫。
I guess I have a plan, too.
不！
No!
【女王的“我們是冠軍”演奏】♪我付了會費♪
[Queen's "We are the Champions" playing] ♪ I've paid my dues ♪
娘炮！
[boy] Pussy!
♪一次又一次♪
♪ Time after time ♪
-準備好了，就準備好了.。-很多事情都很可怕.。
-When you're ready, you're ready. -A lot of things are scary.
♪我已經服完刑了♪
♪ I've done my sentence ♪
你得弄清楚你想要什麼..。
You gotta figure out what you want...
-然後盡你所能得到它.。-鑰匙...。
-and then do what you can to get it. -Keys...
-科爾！-
-Cole! -[engine revving]
十，二。
Ten. Two.
♪我需要繼續，繼續，繼續，繼續♪
♪ And I need to go on and on And on and on ♪
♪我們是冠軍我的朋友♪
♪ We are the champions My friends ♪
♪我們要繼續戰鬥到底♪
♪ And we'll keeping on fighting Till the end ♪
啊……
Yeah!
♪我們是冠軍♪
♪ We are the champions ♪
♪沒時間陪失敗者♪
♪ No time for losers ♪
♪因為我們是冠軍♪
♪ 'Cause we are the champions ♪
怎麼了，希？
What up, Cee?
你開著車進了你家。
You drove a car into your house.
我真沒想到會這樣。
I really didn't see that coming.
你從不告訴我。
You never told me...
星際夢之隊。
your intergalactic dream team.
你沒有問。
You didn't ask.
我應該這樣做的。
I should have.
我通常對那東西很在行。
I'm usually pretty good at that stuff.
阿達瑪上將來領導。
Admiral Adama to lead.
為他的智力和冷靜的頭腦提供資料。
Data for his intelligence and cool head.
捕食者戰鬥。
Predator to fight.
然後是我和你。
Then me and you.
你沒有說我們可以加入。
You didn't say we could add ourselves.
這是科幻小說。你能幹任何事情。
It's science fiction. You can do anything.
嗯...我想這是真的。
Well... I guess that's true.
但你還不明白嗎？
But don't you get it yet?
我是大壞蛋。
I am the big bad.
我愛過你。
I loved you.
我不在乎你的蠢書，也不在乎你的蠢邪教。
I don't care about your dumb book or your stupid cult.
我是個成年人..。
I'm an adult...
因為當我意識到你是個大壞蛋..。
because when I realized you were the big bad...
而你背叛了我。
and you betrayed me
還會傷害其他孩子。
and were just gonna hurt other kids,
我開著偷來的車撞了你。
I drove a stolen car through you.
那個，我給你。
That, I'll give you. [chuckles]
再見，希。
I'll see you, Cee.
再見。
Goodbye.
馬丁內斯。-什麼？
-[Melanie's dad] Martinez. -Yeah?
保護和服務白癡。
Protect and serve, idiot.
這只是一輛車。-保護我的車。
-[Melanie] It's just a car. -Protect my car.
只是輛車！只是輛車！
Just a car?! Just a car?!
別--馬上把你的手給拿開。
Do not-- Put your hand down right now.
-我以為你會開車走。-我不能離開你。
-I thought you were gonna drive away. -I couldn't leave you.
真是一輛破車。
That was such a douche car.
媚蘭，過來。
Melanie, get over here.
回來這裏。馬上。
Get back here. Now.
再見。
Bye.
哦，我的天。
[Melanie's dad] Oh, my God.
剛才你把臉貼在他身上了嗎？想現在去紋身嗎？
Did you just put your face on him? Wanna go get tattoos now?
怎麼回事？
Yo. What happened?
哥們兒，科爾偷了輛車。
Dude, Cole stole a car.
撞到了他的房子。大約50人被殺。
Rammed his house. Killed, like, 50 people.
五十人。
Fifty people. [scoffs]
嘿，我們離開這裏。
[Jeremy] Hey, let's get out of here.
今天，你們。咱們走吧。
Today, y'all. Let's go.
見鬼？
The hell?
辛蒂。
Cindy.
你有見到我的兒子嗎？拜託... 科爾。
-[Mom] Do you have my son? Please... -[Dad] Cole.
親愛的，親愛的。
[Mom] Honey. Honey. Oh, my God.
你沒事吧?
Are you okay? Are you...?
-我沒事。- 你沒事吧？
-I'm okay. -[Dad] Are you all right?
-天啊，怎麼了？-那是血嗎？
-Oh, my God. What happened? -Is that blood?
嘿，怎麼回事？
Hey. What happened?
我不再需要保姆了。
I don't need a babysitter anymore.
♪當我最好的朋友說她失去了男人♪
♪ When my best friend said She had lost her man ♪
♪對她的保姆我以為她在撒謊♪
♪ To her babysitter I thought she was lying ♪
♪我說：“沒有16歲的女學生♪
♪ I said, "No 16-year-old schoolgirl ♪
♪會帶走我這樣的人“♪
♪ Would ever take a man of mine" ♪
♪一直在家陪著我們的孩子♪
♪ Staying home With our baby all the time ♪
♪讓我有點心碎♪
♪ It kept me kind of brokenhearted ♪
♪所以我就去給自己雇了個保姆♪
♪ So I went And hired myself a babysitter ♪
♪那時我的麻煩就開始了♪
♪ And that's when my trouble all started ♪
♪這個16歲的女孩走進來了♪
♪ This 16-year-old chick walked in ♪
♪裙子一直到她的腰♪
♪ With a skirt up to her waist ♪
♪她有一卡車你知道嗎♪
♪ She had a truckload of you-know-what ♪
♪所有這些都到位了嗎♪
♪ And all of it in place ♪
♪我應該知道的，嗯♪
♪ I should have been aware, mm-hmm ♪
♪哦--哦，保姆♪
♪ Ooh-ooh, of the babysitter ♪
♪哦，是的，是的，我應該從跳躍中知道的，是嗎♪
♪ Oh, yeah, yeah I should've known from the jump, yeah ♪
♪她是個男人，嗯♪
♪ She was a man-getter, mm-hmm ♪
♪我應該知道，嗯♪
♪ I should've been aware, uh-huh ♪
♪保姆♪[喊叫聲]。
♪ Of the babysitter ♪ [shouts]
♪跳傘應該知道嗎，是的♪
♪ Should've the known from the jump Yeah ♪
♪是的，她是個男人♪
♪ She was a man-getter Yeah, she was ♪
[模糊的無線電聊天]
[indistinct radio chatter]